PUSHPENDRA CHANDRAVANSHI

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Bhopal, MP, India

+91-916-555-6535

pushpendrachandravanshi4@gmail.com

PROFILE SUMMARY

As a Front End Developer with 1.5 years of experience, I am skilled in building and maintaining user-friendly and visually appealing websites using a variety of technologies, including HTML, CSS, JavaScript and ReactJS. I am a team player and can effectively communicate with both technical and non-technical stakeholders. As a developer I always stay up-to-date on the latest developments in front end development.

SKILLS

HTML5 CSS

Javascript

ReactJS

Tailwind CSS

DSA(C++)

Python

NextJS

Figma

EDUCATION

B. Tech 2020 - 2024

Samrat Ashok Technological Institute, Vidisha

CGPA - 8.2 (Till 5th Semester)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-End Developer

(April 2022 - August 2022)

ADmyBRAND

- Learned new technologies like NextJS, Tailwind CSS, Figma.
- Gain experience with API Integration, React redux and designing tools like Figma
- Gain experience of working in a team at a startup.

Front-End Developer, Python Developer

(August 2022 - October 2022)

WATT

- Worked on website of the startup.
- Used my past experience to manage development team of website.
- · Worked on code for a robot.

Front-End Developer (Open Source Contributer)

(December 2022 - Working)

Score Lab (CodeLabz)

- Worked on UI of CodeLabz website .
- · Gained experience of working on Open Source project.
- https://github.com/scorelab/Codelabz

PERSONAL PROJECTS

News Site

- A news website that fetches news from API and display them properly as cards.
- We can read different news by selecting different category.
- https://github.com/Pushpendra766/theindian-times
- ReactJS/Bootstrap

Bank Website

- An interactive website for bank and with options to signup/login.
- www.bankistdom766.netlify.com
- HTML/CSS/Javascript